https://www.lucoinc.com/privacy-policy

Livestock Handling Equipment& Hog Confinement Units
Cart (0)
Home
::
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Products
Shipping Information
FAQs
About
Customer Service
Luco Manufacturing
705 Cottonwood Street
Strong City, Kansas 66869
Email Signup
Get exclusive customer deals, new product news & special offers
submit
Product Categories
Cattle Equipment & Supplies
Fencing & Supplies
Heating Products & Supplies
Hog Equipment & Supplies
Horse Equipment & Supplies
Livestock Waterers
© 2020 Luco Manufacturing, All Rights Reserved
Are you searching for:
Hog Waterers,Feeding Floors,Hog Confinement Units,Farm Gates,Animal Houses,Livestock Handling Equipment,Ag-Mart Products,Hog Haven Products,TaskMaster Products,Heating Products & Supplies,Fencing & Supplies,Poly Board Sheeting,Wildlife & Deer Supplies,Pet Products & Supplies,Power Tools,Poultry Equipment & Supplies,Livestock Waterers,Horse Equipment & Supplies,Hog Equipment & Supplies,Cattle Equipment & Supplies
